techcitynews.com 2018-05-17

# Privacy & Cookie Policy - UKTN (UK Tech News)

This Privacy and Cookie Policy states what we will do with your Personal Data once you have submitted your details to the site. By submitting your details, you agree to the principles of this policy. We comply with the Data Protection Act 1998. Any information you give to Media Ventures International Limited will be held with the utmost care and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices please contact our Data Manager via email: [marketing@wearemvi.com](mailto:marketing@wearemvi.com).

 **Collection of Information**  
We collect personal information in a number of different ways. These include email inquiry forms which can be found on our contact us page, through data capture forms found on guide or report download pages and through cookies. You can find out more about what cookies are and why we use them further down this document.

 **Use of Personal Information**  
Your personal data will be used by Media Ventures International Limited to communicate with you. This will take the form of emailing you our product newsletters, sending you specially selected Third Party advertising offers, or communicating with you regarding our service so long as you have opted-in to receiving any of the former. Your personal information will not be used for any purpose not directly related to Media Ventures International Limited’s business offering. At any point you can unsubscribe from any or all of our communications by clicking the unsubscribe link which we make available on all our communications. If you have problems doing this you can contact us on 020 7502 8220 and ask to speak with our Data Manager or email [marketing@wearemvi.com](mailto:marketing@wearemvi.com).

 **Data Capture Forms**  
We will send you information according to the preferences you submitted via our data capture form. If you would like to change these preferences at any point, please email us at [marketing@wearemvi.com](mailto:marketing@wearemvi.com) or call us on 020 7502 8220. Alternatively, you can also write to us: Data Manager, WeWork c/o Media Ventures International, 41 Corsham St, London N1 6DR.

On occasion we may market to your products and services related to Media Ventures International Limited’s business offering (including updates to our service offering) and also offers from carefully selected advertisers where you have opted-in to receiving such communications. If at any point you would like to opt-out of receiving communications from us, or you would like to change the channels that we use to contact you, please contact us at [marketing@wearemvi.com](mailto:marketing@wearemvi.com). Additionally, you can unsubscribe from any or all of our communications by clicking the unsubscribe link that is available on all of our communications. Please note that we can only unsubscribe e-mail addresses we know about and not any forwarding or linked addresses from whose accounts a request may be received. To ensure you stop receiving our e-mails, please provide the original e-mail address you signed up with or all addresses you think we may hold.

 **Disclosure of information to companies that form Media Ventures International Limited.**  
Media Ventures International Limited is formed of the following companies: Propertywire.com, Guides and Brochures Ltd, UKTN and has access to Tax Confidential, Company Refs and Mortgage Introducer. To see an up-to-date list of businesses within the group visit [www.wearemvi.com](http://wearemvi.com/).

Media Ventures International Limited may pass your personal data between companies within the group in order to respond to enquiries or for the purpose of marketing communications. In addition, Media Ventures International Limited may on occasion pass your details on to selected third parties outside the group for the purpose of specific marketing communications unless you have opted out of receiving such communications.

 **Other Websites**  
Our website may contain links to other websites that are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you that will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policies which may differ from ours.

 **Subject Access Requests**  
You have the right to see what personal data we hold about you. To obtain a copy of the personal information that we hold about you, please write to us: Data Manager, WeWork c/o Media Ventures International, 41 Corsham St, London N1 6DR. Please be aware that we reserve the right to charge a fee of up to £10 for any such request.

 **Internet-based Transfers**  
Given that the Internet is a global environment, using it to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international scale. This means, for instance, that data you pass to us may be processed outside the European Economic Area, although the data will always be held securely and in-line with the requirements of UK data protection legislation. By communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and consent to our processing of personal data in this way.

 **Cookies**  
A cookie is a small piece of information that is placed on your computer when you visit certain websites. Find out more about the use of cookies on [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). We use cookies to:

  1. remember you when you visit this website to keep track of your browsing patterns and to build up a profile of how you and other users use the website.
  2. make our website work as efficiently as possible.
  3. administer services to you and to advertisers.

Most browsers allow you to turn off cookies. To do this look at the “help” menu on your browser. Switching off cookies may restrict your use of the website and/or delay or affect the way in which it operates.

 **Use of Cookies**  
This website uses cookies. These cookies hold no personal information whatsoever and are destroyed upon leaving the website. You are free to turn cookies off in your browser, but please be aware that in doing so, you will not be able to access sites with member sections. Website logs are analysed to constantly improve the value of the information provided on the website. The website logs are not personally identifiable, and no attempts are made to link them with the individuals who actually use the website. Other than our own site cookies, our advertisers may deliver advertising using cookies. These are used for statistical reference only and do not collect any personal information about you.

 **Third Party Advertising Cookies**  
Most of the advertisements you see on the website are generated by third parties. Some of these third parties generate their own cookies (or web beacons) to track how many people have seen a particular advertisement (or use the services of third parties to do this), and to track how many people have seen it more than once. The third party cookies currently being used on our sites are from Google Analytics. These are:

_utma (expires after 2 years)  
_utmb (expires after 30 minutes)  
_utmc (expires at the end of every browsing session)  
_utmz (expires after 6 months)

These cookies cannot be used to identify an individual; they can only be used for statistical purposes, for example, in providing you with advertisements that are more relevant to your interests. Some of the information gleaned from third party cookies will be aggregated with other anonymous information for statistical purposes. The third party companies that generate these cookies have their own, strict, privacy policies but we don’t have access to these cookies; other than allowing them to be served, we have no role to play in these cookies at all. You can visit the trade body representing these advertising companies for more information on how to opt out of these cookies: [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) We endeavour to take all reasonable steps to protect your Personal Data, but cannot guarantee the security of any Personal Data you disclose online. You accept the inherent security implications of dealing online over the internet and will not hold us responsible for any breach of security unless we have been wilfully negligent.

 **Amendments**  
Please note that this privacy policy is subject to change from time to time. It was last updated in May 2017.
